

PARVEEN SAVITA

Digital Marketer

As a professional digital marketer, I have over 2+ years of experience in the field. I complete my digital marketing course from WsCube Tech. I have developed expertise in SEO, SMM, content writing and among others. My focus on results has allowed me to deliver best services to clients, from increasing website traffic to driving sales. I am dedicated to staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and technologies to ensure continued success.

CONTACT

- +91 9318331978
- ≥ Parveensavit000@gmail.com
- Faridabad, Haryana
 Pincode 121003, Tilpat
 Surdas Colony.

SKILLS

- Search Engine Optimization
- Search Engine Marketing
- Social Media Optimization
- Social Media Marketing
- Content Writing
- Image & Video Designing
- Marketing Strategy
- Branding

PORTFOLIO

Scan For Image Designing



/ Or Click Here.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Digital Marketing Bizgurukul

December 2020 to January 2022 (1 year 1 month)

- Digital Marketing
- Social Media Optimization
- Social Media Marketing.



Digital Marketing

Hi-Pack & Fill Machine Pvt. Ltd.

April 2022 to November 2022 (8 months)

- Digital Marketing (Sales)
- SEO| SEM
- SMO | SMM
- Image & Video Designing
- Content & Blog Writing



Digital Marketing

Indartu Technology Pvt. Ltd

November 2022 to Currently Working

- Digital Marketing
- SEO| SEM
- SMO | SMM
- Image & Video Designing
- · Content & Blog Writing
- Marketing Strategy
- Branding

INTEREST









Research About Tech

Listening Watching
Music Movie

Content Creation

PERSONAL DETAILS

- Father's Name Shr Krishna Savita
- Date of Birth 01-01-2002
- Marriage Status Un-married
- Gender Male
- Nationality Indian

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi

EDUCATION HISTORY



10th Passout Haryana Board

Year of Passing: 2019



12th Passout Haryana Board

Year of Passing: 2021



Bachelor of Commerce (Honours) Delhi University

CERTIFICATIONS



Digital Marketing
Online Course - Bizgurukul



Video Editing Online Course - Bizgurukul



Advance Personality Development Online Course - Bizgurukul



Image Designing
Online Course - Canva